

4/85 S.F.S. Agrawal Farm Mansarovar Jaipur, Rajasthan, India

🛮 (+91) 72-9790-5935 | 🔀 asmita.jaipur@gmail.com | 🎁 www.zedex.me | 🖸 asmigos | 🛅 asmita goswami

"Make the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary _

Current working in start-up company CodeJocks Technologies. 1+ years experience specializing in backend/infrastructure, web development and android development. Super nerd who loves Open Source and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Experience _____

CodeJocks Technologies

Pratap Nagar, Jaipur

ANDROID & WEB DEVELOPER

July 2017 - PRESENT

- Built and deployed overall android applications with frontend and backend which include usage of MongoDB, Express, Angular JS and Node.
- Built website for Ideathon (technical event) which include HTML, CSS3, Bootstrap and Node.
- Built android application with google map integration.

Trainings_____

DVS Info Tech. Training

ANDROID APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT

October 2016 - January 2017

• Attained experience on working and implementation of several android components

Honors & Awards ______ Domestic

2017	Winner, SMART INDIA HACKATHON 2017	Nagpur, India
2017	Finalist, AICTE Vishwakarma Chhatra Awards 2017	Jaipur, India
2017	Runners Up, Subito (Renaissance 2017)	Jaipur, India

Presentation

PRESENTER FOR < ICSCF 2017>

JAIPUR ENGINEERING COLLEGE AND RESEARCH CENTRE

Jaipur, Rajasthan

May 2017

• Real time Data Transmission Techniques used in Multiplayer Gaming

Workshops_____

Android App Development

Jaipur, Rajasthan

ATTAINED HANDS ON EXPERIENCE IN THE FIELD OF ANDROID

2016

DevOps over Linux with AWS

Jaipur, Rajasthan

ATTAINED EXPERIENCE IN THE FIELD OF DEVOPS AND AWS

2017

Writing____

IT Newsletter

Departmental Newsletter

Jan. 2017 - April 2017

CONTENT WRITER

• Writes the article on the latest technical events.

IT Edifier Departmental Magazine

CONTENT WRITER

April 2017 - June 2017 • Writes the article on the latest technical events and hackathons conducted all over the nation.

Program Committees _____

2016	Student Volunteer , Department of Hospitality, Renaissance 2016	Jaipur
2017	Student Coordinator, Catch The Phrase (Technical Event), Renaissance 2017	Jaipur
2017	President, HackSlash Organization	Jaipur
2017	Student Coordinator, IT Hackathon, JECRC College	Jaipur
2017	Student Coordinator, JECRC Hackathon, JECRC College	Jaipur

Education

St. Anselm's Pink City Sr. Sec. School

K-12(FROM K.G. TO 12TH

Jaipur, Rajasthan July 2001 - July 2014

JECRC(Jaipur Engineering College and Research Center)

B.Tech in Information Technology Engineering

Jaipur, Rajasthan July 2015 - PRESENT

Extracurricular Activity_

IT Newsletter (Monthly Departmental Newsletter)

EDITOR

January 2017 - June 2017

Jaipur, Rajasthan

• Gained Experience in the feild of Microsoft Office and Designing.

CAI (Center for Apps and Ideas Club of JECRC)

COORDINATOR

Jaipur, Rajasthan Sep. 2016 - PRESENT

• Learned Android App Development.

HackSlash Organization

PRESIDENT

Jaipur, Rajasthan

August 2017 - PRESENT

• Organization for contributing to open source and focuses on importance of Linux.